<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title>Arran's Blog</title><description>Thoughts, stories and ideas.</description><link>http://blog.arranfrance.com/</link><generator>Ghost 0.5</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2014 00:14:59 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://blog.arranfrance.com/rss/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>Changing Shape</title><description>&lt;p&gt;The past few months for me have been a time of transition. I have a new role at work, a new set of friends, and even a new home. On the whole I love change and the past few months have been incredibly exciting and inspiring for me but what I find most exciting of all is amidst the external changes is the way God has begun to work on me internally.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When I first became a Christian my life was transformed in a radical way. He gave me a new purpose, a new hope, and a new family and with that came a cascade of changes. Some changes were small, like the things I noticed as I walked to school, and other things were larger, like the way I related to people.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For months things changed in my life at a rapid rate but then things began to slow down and as they did I began to wonder whether someone I'd strayed from the path I was on and if I was beginning to get things wrong.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What I've learnt recently though is that there's still plenty of change happening it's just hidden underneath the surface.&lt;/p&gt;</description><link>http://blog.arranfrance.com/changing-shape/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">d231b7e9-2941-4b79-88f3-5c1d5ade095d</guid><category>faith</category><dc:creator>Arran</dc:creator><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2014 21:57:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Blog Quandaries | Scriptogram, Postach.io, Ghost, and Github Pages</title><description>&lt;p&gt;My last &lt;em&gt;three&lt;/em&gt; blog posts have been posted to three different web addresses using three different web services.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Choosing where to host my blog and which service to use has been a bit of an ordeal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I initially started out using &lt;a href="http://scriptogr.am/"&gt;Scriptogram&lt;/a&gt; but their theme support didn't quite cut it. &lt;a href="http://postach.io/"&gt;Postach.io&lt;/a&gt; was my next stop but they removed their Dropbox integration recently forcing me to relocate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I now host my blog on Github Pages using a static version of a locally hosted &lt;a href="http://ghost.org/"&gt;Ghost&lt;/a&gt; blog (following &lt;a href="https://jackpearce.com/have-a-lightning-fast-blog-and-host-it-for-free"&gt;this&lt;/a&gt; guide) saving myself £3/$5 a month over a dynamic implementation. Clunky but cheap.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All in all I've wasted an afternoon and evening trying to get it all working but I also played a little more thoroughly with Github, not quite a worthwhile trade but at least I've learnt a little from the process.&lt;/p&gt;</description><link>http://blog.arranfrance.com/blog-quandaries/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">90835233-070e-4a74-90a3-31b1606fc88b</guid><category>technology</category><dc:creator>Arran</dc:creator><pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2014 19:43:53 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>